scratch99.com 2013-12-29

# Privacy Policy

This policy discloses how personal information is gathered and used by the www.scratch99.com website (referred to as ‘the site’ or ‘this site’ from here on). 

## General

I respect your privacy and I am committed to safeguarding your privacy while using this site. Your personal data will be kept as secure as possible. It will not be shared or sold to other parties. By using this site, you are agreeing to the use of your information as outlined in this Privacy Policy.

## Comments

You are required to enter your name and email address to leave a comment on this site. Your name will be displayed next to the comment, but your email address will NOT be displayed. Your name and email address will NOT be given to any third party, unless required by law.

If you CHOOSE to subscribe to comments, you WILL receive additional comments via email. I RESERVE the right to contact you directly, via email, regarding issues related to your interaction with the site. YOU WILL NEVER BE SPAMMED BY ME.

## RSS Feeds

Subscriptions to RSS feeds are anonymous and no personal information is stored.

## Log Files and Web Statistics

Like most websites, this site uses web statistics software (Google Analytics and Firestats) to collect information about how users interact with the site. This stores information such as IP address, browser type, referring pages, visited pages, exit pages, platform used, date and time of visit, etc. Although this information is collected, it is NOT linked to personally identifiable information, nor is it passed on to any third party.

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. Any information stored by the site in a cookie is only used to provide functionality. It is NOT passed on to any third party.

## Advertisers

Third Party advertising companies are used to display ads on this site. These ads may contain cookies and information may be collected by the advertising companies. I do not have access to this information. Please check the advertisers’ websites for their respective privacy policies. At present, this site uses Google Adsense.

## External Links

This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that this site is NOT responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. This privacy policy applies solely to this site. When you click on a link to another site, we encourage you to read the privacy policy of that site.

## Contact Information

If you have any questions or concerns, please contact me using the [Contact Form](http://scratch99.com/contact/). 

_Privacy policy last updated August 2008._

Last updated on June 29th, 2011 (first published on August 8th, 2008)

**Like this article? Plus One it!**
